export default data15 = [
    {
        id: "q1",
        question: "When was the United Nations set up?",
        options: ["After the First World War.", "After the Second World War.", "Before the First World War.", "Before the Second World War."],
        correct_option: "After the Second World War."
    },
     {
        id: "q2",
        question: "Where is the Giant’s Causeway located?",
        options: ["Scotland", "England", "Wales", "Northern Ireland"],
        correct_option: "Northern Ireland"
    },
     {
        id: "q3",
        question: "What happened to Mary, Queen of Scots, after being sent to prison for 20 years by her cousin Queen Elizabeth I?",
        options: ["She got married.", "She was sent to France.", "She was executed.", "She was sent to Scotland."],
        correct_option: "She was executed."
    },
     {
        id: "q4",
        question: "What is one of the highest-grossing film franchises produced in the UK?",
        options: ["James Bond", "Star Wars", "The Lord of the Rings", "Superman"],
        correct_option: "James Bond"
    },
     {
        id: "q5",
        question: "Who came from the Netherlands to become the British monarch?",
        options: ["William II", "Charles II", "Edward II", "George II"],
        correct_option: "Charles II"
    },
     {
        id: "q6",
        question: "Who can apply for the National Citizen Service programme?",
        options: ["14- and 15-year-olds", "15- and 16-year-olds", "16- and 17-year-olds", "17- and 18-year-olds"],
        correct_option: "16- and 17-year-olds"
    },
     {
        id: "q7",
        question: "Nick Park has won four Oscars for his animated films, including three for films featuring:",
        options: ["Chariots of Fire", "Wallace and Gromit", "Four Weddings and a Funeral", "Women in Love"],
        correct_option: "Wallace and Gromit"
    },
     {
        id: "q8",
        question: "Who was the British scientist who co-discovered the structure of the DNA molecule in the 1950s?",
        options: ["Sir Ian Wilmot", "Keith Campbell", "James Watt", "Francis Crick"],
        correct_option: "Francis Crick"
    },
     {
        id: "q9",
        question: "What percentage of the UK population has a parent or grandparent born outside of the UK?",
        options: ["Around 5%", "Around 10%", "Around 15%", "Around 20%"],
        correct_option: "Around 10%"
    },
     {
        id: "q10",
        question: "How old do you have to be to drive a moped in the UK?",
        options: ["15 years old", "16 years old", "17 years old", "18 years old"],
        correct_option: "16 years old"
    },
     {
        id: "q11",
        question: "Who was the leader of the Labour Party who introduced a Scottish Parliament and a Welsh Assembly?",
        options: ["James Callaghan", "Clement Attlee", "Gordon Brown", "Tony Blair"],
        correct_option: "Tony Blair"
    },
     {
        id: "q12",
        question: "What is the maximum amount you can claim through the small claims procedure in Scotland and Northern Ireland?",
        options: ["£3,000", " £5,000", "£8,000", "£10,000"],
        correct_option: "£3,000"
    },
     {
        id: "q13",
        question: "Which historical monument did William the Conqueror build?",
        options: ["St Paul’s Cathedral", "The Cenotaph", "Dumfries House", "The White Tower"],
        correct_option: "The White Tower"
    },
     {
        id: "q14",
        question: "Who became Prime Minister after Margaret Thatcher and played an important part in the Northern Ireland peace process?",
        options: ["James Callaghan", "John Major", "Tony Blair", "Harold Wilson"],
        correct_option: "John Major"
    },
     {
        id: "q15",
        question: "Who should you contact to report a terrorist activity?",
        options: ["Your local Council.", "Your local MP.", "Your local police force.", "The Prime Minister."],
        correct_option: "Your local police force."
    },
     {
        id: "q16",
        question: "Which Paralympic athlete has won gold medals for swimming at the 2008, 2012 and 2016 Paralympic Games?",
        options: ["Sophie Christiansen", "Ellie Simmonds", "Baroness Tanni Grey-Thompson", "David Weir"],
        correct_option: "Ellie Simmonds"
    },
     {
        id: "q17",
        question: "Each of the UK countries is associated with a flower symbol, which country is associated with the rose?",
        options: ["Wales", "Northern Ireland", "Scotland", "England"],
        correct_option: "England"
    },
     {
        id: "q18",
        question: "Under which name was the movement of opinion against the authority of the Pope during the times of Henry VIII known?",
        options: ["The Spanish Inquisition", "The Holy Wars", "The Reformation", "The Enlightenment"],
        correct_option: "The Reformation"
    },
     {
        id: "q19",
        question: "What did Isaac Newton discover?",
        options: ["Gravity", "Penicillin", "Insulin", "Lightbulb"],
        correct_option: "Gravity"
    },
     {
        id: "q20",
        question: "What kind of movies did Academy Award winner Nick Park specialise in?",
        options: ["Action movies", "Animated movies", "Thrillers", "Horror movies"],
        correct_option: "Animated movies"
    },
     {
        id: "q21",
        question: "Who led a Scottish army against Oliver Cromwell just after England had been declared a Republic?",
        options: ["Charles I", "Charles II", "Henry V", "James I"],
        correct_option: "Charles II"
    },
     {
        id: "q22",
        question: "How many pence are there in a pound?",
        options: ["100 pence", "50 pence", "60 pence", "10 pence"],
        correct_option: "100 pence"
    },
     {
        id: "q23",
        question: "When are local elections for councillors held in most local authorities?",
        options: ["In May", "In March", "In February", "In June"],
        correct_option: "In May"
    },
     {
        id: "q24",
        question: "What sort of stories were collected by the Canterbury Tales written by Geoffrey Chaucer?",
        options: ["Love stories", "Children's stories", "Travellers’ stories", "War stories"],
        correct_option: "Travellers’ stories"
    },
    
]